{
  "header": {
    "status": {
      "statusCode": 0,
      "statusMessage": "MCQ questions data found"
    }
  },
  "body": {
  	"mcq":[
    	   {
            "question":"Which team did Rakesh Kumar lead in his PKL debut?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"U Mumba"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Puneri Paltans"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Patna Pirates"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bengaluru Bulls"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Patna Pirates"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which Puneri player from Season 4 was the most expensive player in the S5 auctions?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Nitin Tomar"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Manjeet Chillar"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Ravinder Pahal"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Deepak Niwas Hooda"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Nitin Tomar"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which Bollywood family owns Jaipur Pink Panthers?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Kapoors"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bachchans"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Salman Khan"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Shah Rukh Khan"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Bachchans"
        },
        {
            "question":"Sandeep Narwal lifted this player off the mat in a display of sheer strength in Season 4 PKL. Who?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Anup Kumar"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Rakesh Kumar"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Meraj Sheyk"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Jasvir Singh"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Meraj Sheyk"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which captain has led his team to the semi-finals to all 4 PKL seasons?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Nitin Tomar"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Manjeet Chillar"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Ravinder Pahal"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Deepak Niwas Hooda"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Manjeet Chillar"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which country do Fazel Athrachali and Abolfazel Maghsoudhalo belong to?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Pakistan"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Iran"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bangladesh"
                },
                {
                    "text":"India"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Iran"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which Indian State is known to produce tons of Kabaddi talent?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Haryana"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Punjab"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Tamil Nadu"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Uttar Pradesh"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Haryana"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which Indian movies does not depict Kabbadi?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Ghilli"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Okkadu"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Pardes"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Dangal"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Dangal"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which is the most common second name in Kabaddi?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Chillar"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Narwal"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Hooda"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bapu"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Narwal"
        },
        {
            "question":"Who is the only Polish player to play in PKL?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Piotr Pamulak"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Michal Spickzo"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Odgen Nash"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Beata Szyd_o"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Michal Spickzo"
        },
        {
            "question":"Mahendra Ganesh Rajput has always been associated with Bengal Warriors ever since he made his debut in season 2. He is representing a team from West this season. Which?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Fortune Giants"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bengal Warriors"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Puneri Paltans"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Uttar Pradesh"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Fortune Giants"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which is the only team to defeat India in World Cup Kabaddi?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Pakistan"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Iran"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bangladesh"
                },
                {
                    "text":"South Korea"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"South Korea"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which foreign country first embraced Kabbadi?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Japan"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Kenya"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Nepal"
                },
                {
                    "text":"England"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Japan"
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the name for Team Tamil Nadu?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Tamil Thalaivas"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Tamil Rajnis"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Tamil Tendulkars"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Tamil Azhagans"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Tamil Thalaivas"
        },
        {
            "question":"How many teams will play in PKL 2017?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"8"
                },
                {
                    "text":"10"
                },
                {
                    "text":"12"
                },
                {
                    "text":"14"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"12"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which is the only team to won PKL twice?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"U Mumba"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Jaipur Pink Panthers"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Patna Pirates"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bengaluru Bulls"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Patna Pirates"
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the wright cutoff to play Kabaddi?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"no limit"
                },
                {
                    "text":"85"
                },
                {
                    "text":"90"
                },
                {
                    "text":"100"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"85"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which season of Pro Kabaddi will kick off on July 28th 2017?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"3"
                },
                {
                    "text":"4"
                },
                {
                    "text":"5"
                },
                {
                    "text":"6"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"5"
        },
        {
            "question":"Crossing this line will give 1 point when there are more than 5 players on mat. Whats the line called?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"Baulk Line"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bonus Line"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Fire Line"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bogie Line"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Bonus Line"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which team won the 1st edition of Pro Kabaddi League?",
            "choices":[
                {
                    "text":"U Mumba"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Jaipur Pink Panthers"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bengal Warriors"
                },
                {
                    "text":"Bengaluru Bulls"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"Jaipur Pink Panthers"
        }
        ]
    }
}